howtoisolve.com 2018-03-19

# Privacy policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at jaysukh.pharma@gmail.com.

At www.howtoisolve.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.howtoisolve.com and how it is used.

 **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.howtoisolve.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.howtoisolve.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **For EU Readers: Cookies law policies**

As Per cookie low in Europe (EU guidelines), I am declaring that howtoiolve.com use cookies to optimize your experience on our website by third party advertisement network (Google adsense), we will assume that you’re happy to receive our cookies. Any query or concern related to guidelines please contact us.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.howtoisolve.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.howtoisolve.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.howtoisolve.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.howtoisolve.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

###  **Advertisement**

We are always believed in high quality (not allowed popup, text pop up) performance as an advertisement. That advertisement can reach and helps to perfect spotlight there you have been found near to this time over the web. We only media between our advertisers and readers that want helps to you by showing best rated products and service over here.

###  **Commenting on our article, policy**

We only accept valuable comment as a picture, link or video on tutorial. If we got any abused text, or the media format then we will block for all time. In case are you sharing any of the links only for marketing or comment flooding purpose then we can take also same action.

###  **Picture/ image policy**

Here, Howtoisolve.com refer some beautiful image for guide purpose only made by self, To easy understand and clear path to resolve as a presentation. If you are getting confusion on looks like same image then contact us on, howtoisolve@gmail.com. We will happy for that!

###  **Article policy**

Here, we are only generating and publishing as a self produce article. We are getting general problems and ideas over the online forums and online discussion time to time.

We glade, if you are not against out privacy policy. These all are normally followed on the entire web that you have been visited till this day. And we are describes all the above points as a privacy policy, confident for all time. Thank you!!
